geisel-software.com 2015-04-29

# Privacy policy | Geisel Software, Inc.

**Privacy Policy**

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the [www.geisel-software.com](http://www.geisel-software.com/) and Geisel Software, Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Geisel Software, Inc. include [www.geisel-software.com](http://www.geisel-software.com/), Geisel Software and [www.geisel-software.com](http://www.geisel-software.com/). The Geisel Software website is a company information site. By using the Geisel Software website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

Geisel Software may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Geisel Software. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Geisel Software website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Geisel Software's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Geisel Software encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Geisel Software so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Geisel Software is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Geisel Software website.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Geisel Software collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

Geisel Software may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Geisel Software and its affiliates. Geisel Software may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Geisel Software does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Geisel Software may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Geisel Software, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Geisel Software may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Geisel Software, in order to determine what Geisel Software services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Geisel Software to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Geisel Software will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Geisel Software or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Geisel Software; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Geisel Software, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The Geisel Software website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Geisel Software pages, or register with Geisel Software site or services, a cookie helps Geisel Software to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Geisel Software website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Geisel Software features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Geisel Software services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Geisel Software secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Children Under Thirteen**

Geisel Software does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Disconnecting your Geisel Software Account from Third Party Websites**

You will be able to connect your Geisel Software account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR GEISEL SOFTWARE ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by visiting their account pages on the particular social network..

**Changes to this Statement**

Geisel Software will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Geisel Software encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Geisel Software is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Geisel Software welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Geisel Software has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Geisel Software at:

Email Address:

Telephone number:

508-853-5310

Effective as of May 25, 2014
